## Vitalii Doroshenko

## **React/React Native Developer**

Summary React/React Native developer with over 4 years of experience in developing

of both web and mobile applications as well as team management and interviewing. Successfully created and deployed to AppStore several mobile

apps, online constructor and CRMplatform. Fluent in English.

Location Kyiv, Ukraine

Phone (WhatsApp, Viber, Telegram) +38 063 342 49 22 E-Mail +38 063 342 49 22 react.sith@gmail.com

Personal page https://doroshenko.netlify.app

**Hard Skills** 

Languages JavaScript (TypeScript), Swift

Frameworks React Native, Expo, React, Next.js, SwiftUI

Back-end / DBs (basics) Node.js, Express, GraphQL, Socket.IO, MongoDB, Firebase

React Native libraries Redux Toolkit, Zustand, Navigation, Reanimated, Video, tvOS, React

Hook Form, Paper, SVG, Lottie, Biome etc

Tools Git, Figma, Jira, CorelDraw

Soft Skills

Languages English C1, Ukrainian/Russian mother tongue

Flexibility Ready to work on any schedule (any time zone, weekends, holidays etc.)

Personal skills Inventive, stress-resistant, responsible

Work experience

Period 15/04/2022 - 31/10/2024

Name and address of employer GAMEDEV LLC, https://slotscity.ua/casino-app

Position React Native Developer

Stack RN CLI, zustand, OneSignal, CodePush etc.

Main responsibilities - Development of online casino application from scratch.

- Full support for deploying an application to the AppStore.

- Conducting interviews during the team expansion process.

Period 19/07/2021 – 24/02/2022

Name and address of employer NashNet, https://www.nashnet.ua

Position React Native Developer

Stack RN CLI, RTK, react-native-tvos etc.

Main responsibilities - Development of mobile TV appliation

Period 21/10/2020 – 15/07/2021

Name and address of employer NMS Group, https://nms-group.agency

Position React, React Native Developer

Stack React, Next.js, React Native, Expo etc.
Main responsibilities - Development of web and mobile apps

·

Education

Period 01/09/1999 - 25/06/2003

Title Bachelor

Principal subjects Mechanical engineering

Educational institution National Technical University of Ukraine (Sikorski Kyiv Politechnic Institute)